http://www.mealsonwheelswny.org/privacy-policy

for partners
Programs & Services
Meal ServicesFind FoodNutrition AssistanceNutrition EducationCommunity Meal Services
Resources
NewsAgency ResourcesBlogNewsletterRequest a SpeakerFor Our Partners
find food assistance near you >
Donate
Search for:
privacy policy
computer tracking & cookies
Our website is not set up to track, collect or distribute personal information not entered by its visitors. Our site logs do generate certain kinds of non-identifying site usage data, such as the number of hits and visits to our site. This information is used for internal purposes by technical support staff to provide better services to the public and may also be provided to others, but again, the statistics contain no personal information and cannot be used to gather such information.
A cookie is a small amount of data that is sent to your browser from a Web server and stored on your computer’s hard drive. FeedMore WNY uses non-identifying cookies to provide easier site navigation and access to forms. You can still use our site if your browser is set to reject cookies. Our cookies do not generate personal data, do not read personal data from your machine, and are never tied to anything that could be used to identify you.
FeedMore WNY / FeedMore WNY Foundation does not share any user information outside of our combined organizations. All computer systems and databases containing private information are password-protected. If you have any questions, concerns or requests related to your user information please contact Lisa Woodring at lwoodring@feedmorewny or 716-822-2005 ext. 3027. Thank you.
donor privacy policy
Thank you for visiting the FeedMore WNY web site. The protection of your privacy is important to us. This privacy statement discloses the privacy practices for the FeedMore WNY website.
Because this site accepts online donations, certain personally identifiable information is collected. The types of information we collect include names, addresses, e-mail addresses, telephone numbers and credit card information. We may also collect other non-personally identifiable information about your computer such as the type of browser you are using or the domain name of your Internet Service Provider.
FeedMore WNY is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We will not sell, share or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement.
FeedMore WNY is committed to protecting the privacy rights of individuals who provide financial support.  We hereby guarantee that names, addresses, personal contact information and donation amounts have not ever been and, in the future, will not be sold or traded with any individual, business or other charities.  In addition, we do not print or publish donors’ names or contribution amounts without their consent.
how we use the information we collect
The personally identifiable information collected by FeedMore WNY site is used to gather online donation information. We may also use this information to send users further details about the FeedMore WNY and its upcoming events, programs and projects. Non-personally identifiable information may be used in aggregate form to analyze the usage of our site and improve site design and interface. This information that we collect will not be disclosed to third parties unless in response to a legal claim or law enforcement agency’s request.
links
This Web site contains links to other sites. FeedMore WNY is not responsible for the privacy practices of other sites. When we link to a new site we will launch a new browser window. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this web site.
security
This Web site has made commercially reasonable efforts to protect our users’ information with appropriate physical and electronic procedures to prevent unauthorized access both online and off-line.
feedback
Users may provide feedback to FeedMore WNY by sending an e-mail to the main office. Any contact information entered when providing feedback will only be used to acknowledge or respond to that feedback.
notification of changes
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes here. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify users by way of an e-mail. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information is collected.
whistleblower policy
FeedMore WNY requires directors, employees and significant volunteers, to observe all laws and regulations that apply to the organization and to practice honesty and integrity in fulfilling their responsibilities.
FeedMore WNY’s reputation and standing in the community is one of its key assets. Management and the Board of Directors are interested in hearing immediately of any concerns of any employee, volunteer or other stakeholder relative to any issue which may threaten this asset.
The organization is committed to achieving compliance with all federal and state laws, regulations governing charitable organizations and corresponding standards and practices.
This policy is intended to provide an avenue to raise concerns with the reassurance that the Food Bank will provide protection from intimidation, harassment, discrimination or other retaliation for whistleblowing in good faith.
The Whistleblower Policy is intended to cover serious concerns that could have an impact on FeedMore WNY from such actions that:
May lead to incorrect financial or poundage reportingAre unlawfulAre not in line with FeedMore WNY policyOtherwise amount to unethical conduct.
read more
